Ragi Dark Cacao Brownie
Walnut Reserve Brownie
Pista, Rose & Cardamom
Seasonal Strawberry & Cacao Brownie
Biscoff Crunch Brownie
Chocolate Wafer Crunch Brownie
Signature Discovery Box — Classic Six
Signature Discovery Box — House Six
Reserve Collection — Classic Nine
Reserve Collection — Six-Flavour Assortment
Three-Piece Brownie Tin
Brownie Tin Flavour Collection
Brownie Tin Flight
Party Brownie Tins
Party Brownie Tubs
Individually Packed Brownies
Little Celebration — 250 g
Occasion Brownie Cake
Ragi Dark Cacao Tea Cake
Pista Cardamom Millet Tea Cake
Dark Cacao Ragi Cupcakes — Box of 6
Pista Cardamom Cupcakes — Box of 9
Cupcake Discovery Collection — Box of 12
Corporate Mini Box — Classic Four
Corporate Mini Box — Ragi & Walnut
Bespoke Corporate Gifting
Seasonal Hamper Collection